Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2008
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Ensemble for Intuitive Music, June 2008, X.; 1 CD-ROM (36 image files in TIFF format)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Michael van Hintzenstern, piano, Daniel Hoffmann, fluegelhorn, Matthias von Hintzenstern, violoncello, and Hans Tutschku, electronics, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 025TIF.tif (Image-file cd10-09)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Michael van Hintzenstern, piano, Daniel Hoffmann, fluegelhorn, Matthias von Hintzenstern, violoncello, and Hans Tutschku, electronics, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 025jTif.tif (Image-file cd10-10)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Michael van Hintzenstern, piano, Daniel Hoffmann, fluegelhorn, Matthias von Hintzenstern, violoncello, and Hans Tutschku, electronics, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 027JPG.tifTIF.tif (Image-file cd10-11)
  - Pianist Hans Tutschku, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 044Hans Tutschku.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-12 (Image-file cd10-12)
  - Pianist Hans Tutschku, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 045.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-13 (Image-file cd10-13)
  - Pianist Hans Tutschku, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 047.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-14 (Image-file cd10-14)
  - Pianist Hans Tutschku, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 048.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-15 (Image-file cd10-15)
  - Pianist Hans Tutschku, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 049.tif (Image-file cd10-16)
  - Pianist Hans Tutschku, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 050Hans Tutschku.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-17 (Image-file cd10-17)
  - Pianist Hans Tutschku, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 053Hans Tutschku.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-18 (Image-file cd10-18)
  - Pianist Hans Tutschku, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 056Hans Tutschku.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-19 (Image-file cd10-19)
  - Pianist Hans Tutschku, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 059Hans Tutschku.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-20 (Image-file cd10-20)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Hans Tutschku, Matthias and Michael von Hintzenstern, and Daniel Hoffmann, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 063TIF.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-21 (Image-file cd10-21)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Michael van Hintzenstern, piano, Daniel Hoffmann, fluegelhorn, Matthias von Hintzenstern, violoncello, and Hans Tutschku, electronics, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 070.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-22 (Image-file cd10-22)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Hans Tutschku, Michael and Matthias von Hintzenstern, and Daniel Hoffmann, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 074.tif---.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-23 (Image-file cd10-23)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Hans Tutschku, Michael and Matthias von Hintzenstern, and Daniel Hoffmann, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 074.tif---xx.tif (Image-file cd10-24)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Hans Tutschku, Michael and Matthias von Hintzenstern, and Daniel Hoffmann, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 075TIF.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-25 (Image-file cd10-25)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Hans Tutschku, Michael and Matthias von Hintzenstern, and Daniel Hoffmann, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 075b-w.tif (Image-file cd10-26)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Matthias and Michael von Hintzenstern, Hans Tutschku, and Daniel Hoffmann, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 080.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-27 (Image-file cd10-27)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Matthias and Michael von Hintzenstern, Hans Tutschku, and Daniel Hoffmann, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 083.tiftif.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-28 (Image-file cd10-28)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Matthias and Michael von Hintzenstern, Hans Tutschku, and Daniel Hoffmann, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 087TIF.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-29 (Image-file cd10-29)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Matthias and Michael von Hintzenstern, Hans Tutschku, and Daniel Hoffmann, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 087TIFb-w.tif (Image-file cd10-30)
  - Daniel Hoffmann playing muted trumpet, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music Daniel Hoffman.jpg In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-31 (Image-file cd10-31)
  - Daniel Hoffmann playing muted trumpet, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music Daniel Hoffman.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-32 (Image-file cd10-32)
  - Daniel Hoffmann playing muted trumpet, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music Daniel Hoffmanb-w.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-33 (Image-file cd10-33)
  - Daniel Hoffmann playing muted trumpet, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music Daniel Hoffmanb-w==.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-34 (Image-file cd10-34)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Hans Tutschku, electronics and Michael von Hintzenstern, piano, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music Hans Tutschke.tif (Image-file cd10-35)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Hans Tutschku, Matthias and Michael von Hintzenstern, and Daniel Hoffmann, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music TIF......tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-36 (Image-file cd10-36)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Michael van Hintzenstern, piano, Daniel Hoffmann, fluegelhorn, Matthias von Hintzenstern, violoncello, and Hans Tutschku, electronics, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music TIF.tif (Image-file cd10-37)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Hans Tutschku, Matthias and Michael von Hintzenstern, and Daniel Hoffmann, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music jpg.tif (Image-file cd10-38)
  - Pianist Hans Tutschku, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Hans Tutschke TIF_.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-39 (Image-file cd10-39)
  - Pianist/composer Hans Tutschku with masterclass students, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Hans Tutschku masterclass send.tif (Image-file cd10-40)
  - Composer Hans Tutschku writing musical example during masterclass, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Hans Tutschku----.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-41 (Image-file cd10-41)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Matthias von Hintzenstern, Hans Tutschku, Michael von Hintzenstern, and Daniel Hoffmann, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: June in Buffalo 09 022.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-42 (Image-file cd10-42)
  - Pianist/composer Hans Tutschku with masterclass students, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: June in Buffalo 09 078.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-43 (Image-file cd10-43)
  - Pianist/composer Hans Tutschku with masterclass students, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Masterclass Hans Tutschka.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-44 (Image-file cd10-44)
  - Pianist/composer Hans Tutschku with masterclass students, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Masterclass Hans Tutschka==.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-45 (Image-file cd10-45)
  - Violoncellist Matthias von Hintzenstern, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Matthias von Hintzenstern.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-46 (Image-file cd10-46)
  - Pianist Michael von Hintzenstern, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Michael v.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-47 (Image-file cd10-47)
  - Overhead shot of Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Michael von Hintzenstern, piano, Daniel Hoffmann, fluegelhorn, Matthias von Hintzenstern, violoncello, and Hans Tutschku, electronics, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: TIF.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-48 (Image-file cd10-48)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Matthias von Hintzenstern, Hans Tutschku, Daniel Hoffmann, and Michael von Hintzenstern, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: ensemble for intuitive music.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-49 (Image-file cd10-49)
  - Pianist/composer Hans Tutschku with masterclass students, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: masterclass Hans Tutschku send.tif (Image-file cd10-50)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Hans Tutschku, Michael and Matthias von Hintzenstern, and Daniel Hoffmann, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: xx.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-51 (Image-file cd10-51)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Hans Tutschku, Michael and Matthias von Hintzenstern, and Daniel Hoffmann, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: xx===.tif (Image-file cd10-52)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
June in Buffalo (Festival) (Buffalo, N.Y.)--Photographs; Composers--Photographs; Music festivals--New York (State)--Buffalo--Photographs; Musicians--Photographs
Genres
Photographs; Portraits
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2000
Mus. Arc. 18
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2000 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2001
Mus. Arc. 19
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2001 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2002
Mus. Arc. 20
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2002 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2003
Mus. Arc. 21
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2003 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2004
Mus. Arc. 25
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2004 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2005
Mus. Arc. 27
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2005 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2006
Mus. Arc. 29
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2006 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2007
Mus. Arc. 38
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2007 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2009
Mus. Arc. 50
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2009 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2010
Mus. Arc. 55
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2010 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2011
Mus. Arc. 56
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2011 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2012
Mus. Arc. 60
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2012 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2013
Mus. Arc. 66
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2013 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2014
Mus. Arc. 67
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2014 June in Buffalo.
June in Buffalo Photograph Collection
A selection of images from the June in Buffalo festivals is available through University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.